[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Both Patrick Swayze and Jennifer Grey were how many years older in real life than their characters in the movie Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "7", "9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Mias worst enemy in the film The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "Lana", "incorrect_answers": ["Fontana", "Anna", "Lilly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous actor said the line This is a weapon; this is for fun.?", "correct_answer": "Sean Penn in Casualties of War", "incorrect_answers": ["Sting in Dune", "Max Von Sydow in Flash Gordon", "Tom Berenger in Platoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the friend and neighbor featured in the documentary Grey Gardens who was an accomplished artist and known as the palmist of East Hampton?", "correct_answer": "Lois Wright", "incorrect_answers": ["Eloise Gardner", "Louise Fletcher", "Madam Louise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the 1994 crime movie Pulp Fiction?", "correct_answer": "Quentin Tarantino", "incorrect_answers": ["Oliver Stone", "Francis Ford Coppola", "Martin Scorsese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Texas Chainsaw Massacre and Poltergeist are some of this directors best known movies.", "correct_answer": "Tobe Hooper", "incorrect_answers": ["John Carpenter", "Ed Wood", "Gordon Parks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many hearts do most octopi have?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "1", "0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the most rare disease.", "correct_answer": "Smallpox", "incorrect_answers": ["Brain tumor", "Schizophrenia", "Glaucoma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The moon phases are the result of the moons rotation around the Earth, causing us to see different parts of the moons surface lit by the sun.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the radial artery located?", "correct_answer": "Forearm", "incorrect_answers": ["Abdomen", "Behind the Knee", "Neck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character in the movie Dirty Dancing said, You just put your pickle on everybodys plate college boy, and leave the hard stuff to me.", "correct_answer": "Johnny", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy", "Max Kellerman", "Neil Kellerman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is amazing but true that sometimes hot water can freeze faster than cold water. What is this effect called?", "correct_answer": "Mpemba Effect", "incorrect_answers": ["Deplembes Effect", "Fourier Effect", "Torricelli Effect"]}]